alipartnership.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy

_AliPartnership.com_ is compliant with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679.

It means that we are open about our methods of tracking and use of the visitors’ personal data, and you can freely check what exactly we’re doing to it.

By using any of our services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and [Terms of Use](https://alipartnership.com/terms-of-service-terms/).

Below, you can read more about our reasons and ways to collect and use your personal details – they are different for our website visitors, company clients, and affiliates.

**I am an AliPartnership website visitor**

AliPartnership website visitors are Internet users who browse any pages on alipartnership.com website and take any actions apart from buying the AliPartnership products or ordering AliPartnership services.

**What personal details we collect from the AliPartnership website visitors**

  * Your email address (in case you voluntarily leave it while downloading informational guides, or subscribing for mass emails, or leaving a comment in the blog section, or sending a query email to the support team)
  * The data about the browser and device you use to navigate the website
  * The way you navigate the website

**Why we collect these details from the AliPartnership website visitors**

The data is collected for the following purposes:

  * Email addresses are used to give you the access to our educational materials, and to inform you about our deals and special offers 
  * The data about your browser and device is used to personalise the website visual appearance, and to let you use the website resources to the full extent
  * The way you navigate the store is analysed in order to let us research the ways to improve the website interface for a greater users’ satisfaction

**What personal details of the AliPartnership website visitors we share with third parties**

In order to provide you with the highest quality services, AliPartnership partners with several external companies (‘third parties’) that also receive some of the collected personal details:

  * Aweber (mass mailing service) uses the collected email addresses in order to create a database out of them, and to arrange mass delivery of our company newsletters
  * Google Analytics (web analytics tool) tracks your on-site behavior (the date of your visit to the website, the length of each session, the pages you have visited, the number of times you access the website within any month, and similar details) in order to help us understand the needs and actions of our website visitors, and improve our performance accordingly.

**I am an AliPartnership company client**

An AliPartnership company client is an individual who has purchased at least one product or ordered at least one service from alipartnership.com website.

**What personal details we collect from the AliPartnership clients**

  * Your first name and last name
  * Your email address and/or Skype contact details
  * The contents of your order(s) (the exact set of AliPartnership services ever ordered by you)
  * Your payment details
  * The data about the browser and device you use to navigate the website
  * The way you navigate the store 

**Why we collect these details from the AliPartnership clients**

The data is collected for the following purposes:

  * Your first name and last name are used to verify your identity when you access the products developed for you by AliPartnership team
  * Email addresses and/or Skype details are used to establish and maintain contact with you throughout the whole process of rendering the ordered service and providing the post-purchase support
  * The data about the contents of your order is used to render you the service(s) you have purchased, and to keep track of them in order to be able to answer any of your questions that may arise during the post-purchase support
  * Your payment details are used to perform fraud screening and process the orders
  * The data about your browser and device is used to personalise the website visual appearance, and to let you use the website resources to the full extent
  * The way you navigate the store is analysed in order to let us research the ways to improve the website interface for a greater users’ satisfaction

**What personal details of the AliPartnership clients we share with third parties**

In order to provide you with the highest quality services, AliPartnership partners with several external companies (‘third parties’) that also receive some of the collected personal details:

  * Aweber (mass mailing service) uses the collected email addresses in order to create a database out of them, and to arrange mass delivery of our company newsletters
  * Google Analytics (web analytics tool) tracks your on-site behavior (the date of your visit to the website, the length of each session, the pages you have visited, the number of times you access the website within any month, and similar details) in order to help us understand the needs and actions of our website visitors, and improve our performance accordingly.
  * Stripe (online payment processing service) uses your credit card details in order to charge you for the order and transfer the money to AliPartnership company

**I am an AliPartnership affiliate**

An AliPartnership affiliate is an individual that has agreed to the terms of [AliPartnership Affiliate program](https://alipartnership.com/affiliates/) and registered as an affiliate in order to promote AliPartnership services by referring clients to the company.

**What personal details we collect from the AliPartnership affiliates**

  * Your first name and last name
  * Your email address
  * Your PayPal account details
  * The data about the browser and device you use to navigate the website
  * The way you navigate the store 

**Why we collect these details from the AliPartnership clients**

The data is collected for the following purposes:

  * Your first name and last name are used to verify your identity when you access your personal affiliate account
  * Email addresses are used to establish and maintain contact with you throughout the whole time of you being an AliPartnership affiliate
  * Your PayPal details are used to send you affiliate commission payments
  * The data about your browser and device is used to personalise the website visual appearance, and to let you use the website resources to the full extent
  * The way you navigate the store is analysed in order to let us research the ways to improve the website interface for a greater users’ satisfaction.

**How we protect your personal information**

  * Your personal information is only used by a limited number of AliPartnership company employees who are eligible to access such data, and are obliged to keep the personal details and financial information strictly confidential.
  * We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers. Personal information that we store is subject to security and access controls, such as username and password authentication.
  * According to our customised settings, Google Analytics (web analytics tool) deletes the gathered information on the website users’ behavior in 2 years since every particular visitor’s last access to the website.

##### **How we use cookies**

Cookies are small files that are transferred to your computer through your Web browser. With the help of the cookies, AliPartnership site remembers you and recognises your last activity on the website in order to improve its own performance.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

  * To analyse your browser (this way, the website adapts to your device specifics)
  * To remember the contents of your order (this way, we understand your preferences and address your requests more efficiently)
  * To get generalized data on the AliPartnership website traffic and site interaction (this way, we understand what better website experiences and additional tools we can introduce further)

If you keep browsing our website after reading this Privacy Policy, you give us the consent to use your personal details for the purposes explained above.

If you don’t agree to these terms, please leave the website.

You can email us at [support@alipartnership.com](mailto:support@alipartnership.com) and ask:

  * To receive the copy of your personal details we have collected
  * To delete your personal details from our system
  * To withdraw your consent (if you previously agreed to provide us with the data, but then changed your mind)

Thank you for your cooperation!

_This document was last updated on May 24, 2018_
